A Guide to the Larry Levis papers, 1974-2006 M 426
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series 4: Academic Files, 1980-1996
  - Iowa Writers' Workshop - letter, course proposal, newsletters, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Tufts University - letter, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - University of Alabama - tenure evaluation for Robin Behn, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - University of Missouri - correspondence and forms, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - University of Utah - administrative materials, correspondence, and course materials, 1983-1988, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - University of Utah - student work, 1985-1990, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - administrative materials, 1992-1996, undated (Box 27-28, Folder 12-1)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - course materials, 1992-1995, undated (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - Hurston/Wright award ceremony flyer and winning entries, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - MFA program applications, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - MFA program posters, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - student work, 1993-1996, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - student work, Advanced Poetry Writing, 1994, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - student work, thesis draft, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - Writers' Conference and Workshop, 1987-1990, undated (Box 29-30, Folder 5-1)
  - Warren Wilson College - administrative materials and course description, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Warren Wilson College - student correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
  - Warren Wilson College - student work, 1993-1996, undated (Box 30-31, Folder 5-4)
  - Unidentified administrative materials, 1985-1996, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified course materials, 1992-1993, undated (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - Unidentified student work, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Business and Personal Files, 1980-2000
  - Appointment books, 1987-1995 (Box 32, Folder 4-6)
  - Bill of sale for television, draft, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Boots (Box 40)
  - Bread Loaf Writers' Conference, announcement, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Drawings, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Family photographs, circa 1977-1983, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - [Funeral], VHS cassette tape, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Glenn, Ann, Individual Artist Fellowship proposal, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Guestbooks, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
  - International Literary Manifestation "Sarajevo Poetry Days," certificate of appreciation, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - "Larry Levis Funeral," VHS cassette tape, circa 1996 (Box 33-34, Folder 10-1)
  - Larry Levis photo shoot with Erin Seals, photographic materials, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Larry Levis, photographs, 1955, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - "Larry poems promised and out," list, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - "Levis Ranch Master," DVD disc, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Loan agreement with Lee Glass, handwritten, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Market Street Oyster Bar cards, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - "Memorial Service," VHS cassette tape, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Memorial service program, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous materials, 1986, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - "Mom, Ranch in Spring," VHS cassette tape, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Fellowship Panel, correspondence, 1985-1987, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Obituary, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Office of Larry Levis, photographs, proofs, and related materials, 1997-2000, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Passport, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Photographs by Patricia Shepardson, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - To do list, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Travel, photographs, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified notes, 1987, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified photographs and related materials, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - University of Missouri, identification card, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - "Unsolved Mysteries; H. H.," VHS cassette tape, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Utah Original Writing Competition, awards, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Vita, Ann Glenn, circa 1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Vitae, circa 1980-1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Voter Registration Card, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Writing workshops, photographs, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Series 6: Born Digital Materials
  - "AG 91," 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - "Back up Doc V, Doc I," [disk 4], 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - "Back Up MS Writer System," [disk 2] 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - "CLLT, Spr. 1991," 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - "Documents 1," [disk 3] 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - "Larry," 3.5 inch floppy disks (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - "Levis," 4.25 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - "MS Writer System," 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - "Poems and Related Materials from 'Texts,'" 3.5 inch floppy disks (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - "Porlone's Levis Poetry," 3.5 inch floppy disks (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - "Porlones Levis Poetry," 4.25 inch floppy disk (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - "Texts," 3.5 inch floppy disks (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - [Untitled] 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - "Untitled, Prose, Chemistry (Creature), and Pastiche," [disk 1] 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - "Virus Check," 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "Warren Wilson Letters from 'Texts,'" 3.5 inch floppy disks (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "WP 5.0 Learning," 4.25 inch floppy disk (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Series 7: Sheila Brady Materials, 1975-2005
  - Academic files: unidentified student work, 1995-1996, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Academic files: Virginia Commonwealth University MFA program posters, photocopied, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Academic files: Warren Wilson College - correspondence and student evalutions, 1996, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Academy of American Poets, 1996-2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Boston, Bruce, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Buckley, Christopher, 1998-2003, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Cornis-Pope, Marcel, Virginia Commonwealth University, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Costanzo, Gerald, Carnegie Mellon University Press, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Courtright, Frederick, The Permission Company, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Dana, Robert, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Eastern Washington University, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Fine, Richard, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Flinn, Mary, 1996-1999 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Glenn, Ann, 1996-2004 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Grimm, Amy, Warren Wilson College, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Hearle, Kevin, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Levine, Philip, 1997-2001 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Levis family, 1975-1997, undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Murphy, Genie, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Prufer, Kevin, Central Missouri State University, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Seattle Review, 1996-1998 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Soldofsky, Alan, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Timothy, Joscelyn, International Biographical Centre, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: University of Michigan Press, 1999-2005 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: University of Pittsburgh Press, 1996-2005, undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Venable, John, 1996, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Williams, Fielding L., 1998 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Yogi, Stan, California Council for the Humanities, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, other: Seals, Erin and Mary Flinn, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - High school diploma, Larry Levis, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Memorial service materials, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous materials, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Obituaries, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Printed materials, 1986-1997, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Reviews, 1998-2002, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Writings: Black Freckles "Three Illustrations", undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Writings: Elegy poem drafts, 1992-1996, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Writings: Elegy manuscript, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Writings: Selected Levis manuscript with cover letter, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Writings: The Gazer Within poem drafts with cover note, undated (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
  - Writings: The Gazer Within manuscript, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Writings: The Gazer Within manuscript with cover letter, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Writings: List of poems and prose by Larry Levis sorted and sent to Phil Levine, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Writings: Marshall, Randy, "Suite: Larry Levis," draft, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Writings: McNair, Wesley C. "The Art and Craft of Poetry: An Anthology of Poems and Writing about Poetry", 1997 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Writings: Smith, David, "Larry Levis: Johnny Dominguez, A Letter", undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Writings: Voigt, Ellen Bryant, "What I Remember of Larry's Dream of Yeats", undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Writings: Williams, Marty, "Leaving: for Larry Levis", undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Series 8: Collected Materials, 1996
  - Posters, 1996, undated (Box Drawer 1)